http://www.bank-northwest.com/about/site-information/privacy-security

Dashboard
HyperLink
Scheduled Maintenance Routine
To maintain the highest level of service for our customers, we will be performing a scheduled maintenance routine on Saturday, December 12th from 10:00 pm CST to  12:00a.m. CST. During this time, Personal and Business Online & Mobile Banking access will be unavailable. Thank you!
COVID-19 Updates & Hours PPP Loan Forgiveness Schedule An Appointment
Search
Home
Search
Our Company
Northwest Bank
Northwest Wealth Management
Northwest Insurance Services
Northwest Financial Corporation
Enroll Now
Forgot Password?
Forgot Password?
Questions? Contact your local Treasury Representative
Schedule An Appointment | You can request an in-person or over the phone appointment at any of our bank locations, please complete this form and a banker will follow up with you.
Quick Links
ATM Locator
General Information
Make a Credit Card Payment
Northwest Cares
Re-order Checks
Sign-Up For Our Enewsletter
E-Banking Support:
Call 1-888-969-1265, Monday through Friday 7AM-7PM and Saturdays 9AM-1PM CST.
(Internet/Mobile Banking and BillPay)
General Customer Support
Call 1-800-678-4105, Monday through Friday 7AM-7PM and Saturdays 9AM-1PM CST.
Check Our Rates Apply Now Sign-Up for Rate Watch
Latest Security News
Cardmember Service: For questions about your Northwest Bank Credit Card or to report a Lost or Stolen Card 24-Hour Cardmember Service: 800-558-3424
Make a Credit Card Payment.
Search
Personal
Featured
Protect & Manage Your Credit
Access your credit score* along with personalized tips to improve or maintain your already great score with Credit Sense. Follow your credit score* through your online or mobile banking!
Learn More!
Mobile Wallets
Real Life Made Real Simple. Welcome to the new way to pay! Quickly, conveniently and securely make mobile payments.
In stores. On the web. Within apps.
Get Started Today
Personal
Checking
Savings / CDs
E-Banking
Mobile Banking
Debit / ATM Card
Anytime Access Card
Featured
Biz Buzz Blog!
Focused on helping you grow your business. Learn from the success stories of others and to get useful ideas and information.
See The Buzz
Positive Pay
Positive Pay from Northwest Bank allows you to protect your business account from unauthorized transactions.
Benefits of Positive Pay
Business
Meet Our Business Bankers
Meet Our Treasury Service Representatives
Loans
Checking
Credit Cards
Savings
Equipment Leasing
Treasury Services
Non Processing Days
The Beneficial Ownership Rule
Mortgage
Featured
Home Loans Just Got Easier!
Get pre-qualified, view your progress, securely upload documents and message your Mortgage Lender!
Download Today!
Now Available!
Stay on top of your credit report! Now you can get access to your free credit monitoring that let's you check your score on demand!*
Check It Out!
Mortgage
Apply Today
Meet Our Mortgage Bankers
Credit Sense
Mortgage Loan Programs
Home Equity | Lines of Credit
Rate Watch Sign-Up
The Safe Act
Financial Calculators
Test
Agriculture
Featured
Biz Buzz Blog | Agribusiness
Focused on helping you grow your business.  Learn from the success stories of others and get useful ideas, tips and information.
See The Buzz
Ruraliving Home Mortgage Program
Our RuraLiving® Home Mortgage program exemplifies competitive pricing and effective products designed specifically for country home living.
Learn More
Agriculture
Loans
Meet Our Ag Bankers
Private Banking
Featured
Exclusive Deposit Accounts
Our custom banking products and services can help you capitalize on assets, manage liquidity, and strengthen your balance sheet.
Explore Our Solutions
Debit/ATM Cards
Enjoy the convenience of our easy to use Northwest Private Banking Debit Cards at no cost to you!
See the Benefits
Private Banking
Convenient Banking Services
Debit/ATM Cards
Benefits of Private Banking
Meet Our Private Bankers
Wealth Management
Featured
Why Use a Financial Advisor?
Our advisors have the ability and the time to evaluate your portfolio investments, meet with you to discuss objectives, and help you get the most from your investments.
Meet Our Advisors
Advice and Guidance
The essence of who we are and what we do comes to life through the experience we deliver to our clients everyday. Whether your goals are short or long term we can help you with a comprehensive wealth management plan that supports your goals.
Learn More
Wealth Management
Insurance
Locations
Newsroom
Employment
Contact
Font Size:
S
M
L
XL
Home /
About /
Site Information /
Privacy & Security
Meet our Customer Service Team
We respect your right to confidentiality and take every possible measure to ensure that your personal information remains personal. In short, we work hard to earn your confidence and preserve your trust.We value your business and hope you will remain with us for many years to come. If you ever have questions or concerns about the integrity of your account information - please don't hesitate to give us a call or come in to talk to our staff.This privacy disclosure is being issued to comply with the provisions of the Gramm-Leach-Bailey Act governing the privacy of consumer financial information. Northwest Bank Privacy Policy
Customer Identification Notice Internet Privacy Policy Kid's Privacy PolicyCustomer Identification NoticeIMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT PROCEDURES FOR OPENING A NEW ACCOUNT To help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, federal law requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who opens an account. What this means to you: when you open an account, we will ask for your name, address, date of birth, and other information that will allow us to identify you. We may ask to see your driver's license or other identifying documents.Internet Privacy PolicyIn continuing our commitment to provide quality service to our customers, Northwest Bank has adopted the following privacy statement for officers, directors and employees. This privacy statement applies to individuals (consumers) and Northwest Bank reserves the right to amend it at any time.Our Internet Web SiteVisitors to the Northwest Bank web site remain anonymous. We do not collect personal identifying information about site users, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Standard software is used to collect and store ONLY the following non-identifying information about our visitors: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or iastate.edu if you are connecting from Iowa State University’s domain); the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. If you submit an online application, it will be transmitted over a secure connection using encryption and will alert you to this fact. This is the case where confidential information, such as your account number or social security number is requested. Visitors may elect to provide us with personal information via e-mail or our feedback form. This information is used internally, as appropriate, to handle the sender’s request and manage the Northwest Bank web site. It is not disseminated or sold to other organizations. Visitors should, however, keep in mind that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If you do not agree with the use of this information, or are not comfortable with the level of privacy, please use the clear button in on-line forms, or cancel an e-mail before it is sent. Visitors should call us directly at 800.678.4105 if requests or statements include sensitive or private information, such as your account numbers, credit card numbers or social security number. Northwest Bank will never ask you for your Personal Identification Number (PIN) for your Northwest Bank ATM card or Debit card. If you are asked for this information, please call 800.678.4105 and report it to our Deposit Services Department immediately.Our Collection, Use and Retention of Customer InformationWe collect, use and retain information about our customers only where we reasonably believe it would be useful in administering our business, and providing products, services and other opportunities to our customers. We may collect and retain information available from public records, market research and credit reports, as well as information you provide to us, only for specific business purposes. We use information to protect and administer our customers’ records, accounts and funds, to comply with certain laws and regulations, to help design or improve our products and services, and to understand your financial needs and provide you quality products and outstanding service. If you send us an e-mail, we may retain the content of the e-mail and your e-mail address in order to respond to questions or concerns you may have expressed.Our Maintenance of Accurate InformationWe have implemented procedures to help assure that our customers’ financial information is accurate, current and complete in accordance with commercially reasonable standards. While some procedures are required by federal or state law, we also have procedures for responding to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner, and to update information and remove old information. Customers should notify us immediately at 800.678.4105 or 1607 W. 18th St. Spencer, IA 51301 if they receive information regarding their relationship with us that they believe to be inaccurate.Limited Employee Access to InformationWe have procedures and security levels that limit employee access to personally identifiable information to those with a business reason to know such information. The importance of confidentiality and customer privacy is addressed through compliance training and other sources on an on-going basis. Appropriate disciplinary measures are taken to enforce employee privacy responsibilities.Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Outside Third PartiesAt times it is necessary to provide personally identifiable information about our customers to a third party such as a vendor or service company we hire to provide support or services for one or more of our products. These vendors and service companies agree to safeguard our confidential customer information and must abide by applicable law. We may also share customer information with affiliates in accordance with federal banking regulations.Protecting ChildrenNorthwest Bank does not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly conduct on-line marketing to children. We recognize that protecting children’s identities and privacy on-line is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the on-line industry and with parents.If you believe Northwest Bank has misused information obtained through our relationships with you or through our web site, or if you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at 1607 W. 18th Street, Spencer, IA 51301, to resolve any disputes.For additional information concerning Northwest Bank’s customer privacy policies, please see the following notice:Our Privacy Disclosure PolicyWe have never shared nonpublic personal information except as permitted or required by law, and we will continue to protect your privacy.Categories of Information That We May CollectWe collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as: your name, address, social security number, assets, and income. Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as: your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage. Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as: your creditworthiness and credit history.CookiesWe may also collect information from you when you visit our web site through the use of cookies, which are pieces of information stored directly on the computer you are using. Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a web site or information that allows customization of a web site for your use. Anytime a cookie is used, personal information is encrypted for our use only and protected from third party access.Categories of Information That We DiscloseWe do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted or required by law.Disclosure As Permitted By LawWe may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to affiliates, service providers (for example - check printing companies, data processing companies) and companies that perform marketing services on our behalf (for example - bulk mailing companies, direct marketing companies, market research firms, and marketing consultants) or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements (for example - financial service providers, including other banks, insurance underwriters and agents, securities brokers or dealers, investment companies or mortgage companies).Confidentiality and SecurityWe restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your non-public personal information.    This is the web site of Northwest Bank.Our address is 1607 W. 18th Street, Spencer, IA 51301We can be reached via e-mail at info@bank-northwest.com.Our telephone number is 800.678.4105.Northwest Bank Site Operators:Marketing DirectorMarketing AssistantsInformation Collected:We respect the privacy of children and do not collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities we offer at our web site. With respect to our online information collection practices from children under 13 years of age, we collect the following types of personal information directly from children online: e-mail address, first and last name, age and telephone number. Please note that parents may consent to the above collection and use of information without necessarily consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties. With respect to the collection by other organizations of personal information from children at our site, our policy is: we do not have any agreements with outside organizations to collect personal information at our site.Use and Sharing of Information:The information we collect from children is used to respond to children's specific requests to participate in activities such as contests or sweepstakes. We do not share children's personal information with anyone other than those who provide support for the internal operations of the web site and our agents (e.g., contractors who provide fulfillment services or technical support to the web site). All third parties with whom we share information have agreed to maintain security and integrity of personal information.Parental Review:Parents can review the information that we have collected from their children online, prevent the further use, collection or maintenance of such information; or direct the deletion of their children's personal information by calling us at the telephone number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above address.     top
View Navigation
Personal
Business
Mortgage
Agriculture
Private Banking
Wealth Management
Insurance
Copyright ©2020. Northwest Bank. All Rights Reserved.
